<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ConvertFrom-SourceTable on Power$nippets</title>
    <link>https://powersnippets.com/convertfrom-sourcetable/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ConvertFrom-SourceTable on Power$nippets</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 15:00:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://powersnippets.com/convertfrom-sourcetable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Read Me</title>
      <link>https://powersnippets.com/convertfrom-sourcetable/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://powersnippets.com/convertfrom-sourcetable/readme/</guid>
      <description>ConvertFrom-SourceTable Converts a fixed column table to objects.
The ConvertFrom-SourceTable cmdlet creates objects from a fixed column source table (format-table) possibly surrounded by horizontal and/or vertical rulers. The ConvertFrom-SourceTable cmdlet supports most data types using the following formatting and alignment rules:
Data that is left aligned will be parsed to the generic column type which is a string by default.
Data that is right aligned will be evaluated.
Data that is justified (using the full column with) is following the the header alignment and evaluated if the header is right aligned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Source &amp; download</title>
      <link>https://powersnippets.com/convertfrom-sourcetable/source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://powersnippets.com/convertfrom-sourcetable/source/</guid>
      <description>The ConvertFrom-SourceTable script can be installed from the PowerShell Gallery:Install-Script -Name ConvertFrom-SourceTable As it concerns a standalone script, installation isn&#39;t really required.If you don&#39;t have administrator rights, you might just download the script (or copy it) to the required location.You might than simply invoke the script using PowerShell dot sourcing:. .\ConvertFrom-SourceTable.ps1 For source code versions, testers history etc., see the ConvertFrom-SourceTable project site on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>